bukmark.net 2015-06-10

# Privacy Policy

**What is this Privacy Policy for?**

At BizTekMojo.com we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document communicates in detail the types of information collected and recorded by BizTekMojo.com and other third party services and how BizTekMojo.com uses the information it collects.

If you need more information or have any questions about this privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at support [at] cw-rw.com

**Website:**

BizTekMojo.com and its owners take extreme care in regards to user privacy and ensures that every step is taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience. All our content is available anonymously and BizTekMojo.com does not collect personally identifiable information.

**Use of Cookies:**

All content on BizTekMojo.com is available anonymously. Visitors to BizTekMojo.com do not need to register or login to our site to access our content. We do not collect user data or email addresses. As such BizTekMojo.com does not collect or store any personally identifiable information about our visitors. We are proud to have all our content available anonymously.

However, third party vendors, including Google and Media.net, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to BizTekMojo.com. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our site's visitors based upon their visit to BizTekMojo.com and/or other sites across the internet.

Visitors accessing BizTekMojo.com may opt out of using the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). Alternatively, you can-opt out by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance's (DAA) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising by clicking [here](http://www.aboutads.info/).

**Our Advertising Partners:**

Our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. We are currently partnering with Google's DoubleClick, AdSense and Media.net advertising networks. The privacy policy for Google can be found by clicking [here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on BizTekMojo.com which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site's third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

BizTekMojo.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. BizTekMojo.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable these cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. However, some web sites may not function properly without cookies. You can find more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers at the browsers' respective websites. [What are Cookies?](http://www.privacypolicyonline.com/what-are-cookies/)

**Use of Google Analytics:**

BizTekMojo.com utilizes Google analytics' Display Feature to collect data about internet traffic via Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers. We use data from Google analytics for statistical and cumulative reporting about visits to our site. In addition, we also use Demographic and Interests reporting from Google analytics to provide relevant ads based on age, gender and interests.

As BizTekMojo.com does not collect any personally identifiable information, we cannot and will never merge any personally identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information collected through third party advertising products or features, such as Google's DoubleClick, Media.net or AdSense.

You can opt out of Demographic and Interests reporting from Google Analytics Display Advertiser Feature by changing your [Ads settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). In addition Google has created a browser add-on to allow site visitors to opt-out of Google Analytics reports. The browser add-on can be found by clicking [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

**Use of Disqus:**

BizTekMojo.com uses Disqus to allow site visitors to add comments. If you submit any comments on our site you hereby agree to the privacy policy of Disqus, which can be found by clicking [here](https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466259-privacy-policy).

You can opt-out of information collected by Disqus by clicking [here](https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/1657951).

**Social Media Platforms:**

Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and its owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively.

Site visitors are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate / engage upon them with due care and caution in regards to their own privacy and personal details. This website nor its owners will never ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email.

BizTekMojo.com may use social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question. Site visitors are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account.

**External Links:**

Although this website only looks to include quality, safe and relevant external links, users are advised to adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this website. (External links are clickable text / banner / image links to other websites).

The owners of this website cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite their best efforts. Site visitors should therefore note that they click on external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.

**Contact and Communication:**

Visitors contacting this website and / or its owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use.

BizTekMojo.com and its owners use any information submitted to provide you with further information about the products / services we offer or to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have submitted. Your details are not passed on to any third parties.

**Consent:**

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy:**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose.
